[
	{
		"question": "How many seas are there in the world",
		"options": [
			"Three",
			"Five",
			"Seven",
			"Nine"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "Which is the largest fish in the world?",
		"options": [
			"Orca",
			"Great White Shark",
			"Whale Shark",
			""
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "How much tentacles do an octopus have?",
		"options": [
			"Six",
			"Eight",
			"Ten",
			"Twelve"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "What are a group of fishes called?",
		"options": [
			"School",
			"Pack",
			"Shallow",
			"Flock"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "What does most fishes breath through",
		"options": [
			"Skin",
			"Lungs",
			"Gills",
			"Tail"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "Which sea animal produce pearls?",
		"options": [
			"Crab",
			"Blue Whale",
			"Starfish",
			"Oyster"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "Which undersea creatures are known for making electricity?",
		"options": [
			"Tiger Shark",
			"Electric Eel",
			"Puffer Fish",
			"Flying Fish"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Is coral a plant or animal?",
		"options": [
			"Animal",
			"Plant",
			"Neither",
			"Both"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the natural habitat of Clownfish?",
		"options": [
			"Kelp Forest",
			"Coral Reef",
			"Open Ocean",
			"Lakes"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Where does the Seahorse lay eggs?",
		"options": [
			"Carried by the male",
			"Carried by the female",
			"Laid on the coral reef",
			"Laid on the seabed"
		],
		"answer": 0
	}
]